{"Quiz":[
  {
    "question": "Let X = {2, 4, 5, 6}   Y = {3, 4, 7, 8}   Z = {5, 6, 7, 8}, find (X - Y) ∪ (Y - X)",
    "options": [
      "{2, 3, 5, 6, 7, 8}",
      "{3, 4, 7, 8}",
      "{3, 4, 5, 6}",
      "{1, 2, 3, 4, 5}"
    ],
    "correctOption": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Let ξ = {1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7} and A = {1, 2, 3, 4, 5} B = {2, 5, 7} show that (A ∩ B)' = A' ∪ B'",
    "options": [
      "L.H.S. = R. H. S = {6}",
      "{1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 7}",
      "L.H.S. = R. H. S = {1, 3, 4, 6, 7}",
      "{2, 5}"
    ],
    "correctOption": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Let P = {a, b, c, d}   Q = {b, d, f}   R = {a, c, e} verify that (P ∪ Q) ∪ R = P ∪ (Q ∪ R)",
    "options": [
      "{a, b, c, d, e, f}",
      "{d}"
    ],
    "correctOption": 0
  },
  {
    "question": " Let A be {1, 2, 3, 4}, U be set of all natural numbers, then U-A'(complement of A) is given by set.",
    "options": [
      "{1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, ....}",
      "All of the above",
      "{5, 6, 7, 8, 9, ......}",
      "{1, 2, 3, 4}"
    ],
    "correctOption": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "A…………. is an ordered collection of objects.",
    "options": [
      "Relation",
      "Proposition",
      "Set",
      "Function"
    ],
    "correctOption": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the cardinality of the set of odd positive integers less than 10?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "24",
      "01"
    ],
    "correctOption": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the cardinality of the set of odd positive integers less than 10?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "5",
      "20",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctOption": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "The range of function f(x) = sin(x) is (-∞∞, ∞).",
    "options": [
      "False",
      "True"
    ],
    "correctOption": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "For two sets C and D the set (CD) n D will be",
    "options": [
      "C",
      "D",
      "Null",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "correctOption": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "The bit string for the set {2, 4, 6, 8, 10} (with universal set of natural numbers less than or equal to 10) is",
    "options": [
      "1010101010",
      "0101010101",
      "0010010101",
      "1010010101"
    ],
    "correctOption": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "If C = {1} then CX (CX C) = (CX C) X C the given statement is true or false.",
    "options": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "correctOption": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Let C = {1,2,3,4} and D = {1, 2, 3, 4} then which of the following hold not true in this case?",
    "options": [
      "C-D=D-C",
      "C-D=0",
      "CUD=CnD"
    ],
    "correctOption": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Let C = {1,2,3,4) and D = {1, 2, 3, 4} then which of the following hold not true in this case?",
    "options": [
      "C-D=D-C",
      "C-D = 0",
      "CUD Cn D",
      "CnD=C-D"
    ],
    "correctOption": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "{x: x is an integer neither positive nor negative} is",
    "options": [
      "Non-empty and Finite set",
      "Non-empty set",
      "Empty set",
      "Finite set"
    ],
    "correctOption": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Let C and D be two sets then which of the following statements are true? i)CUD=DUC, ii)Cn D D n C",
    "options": [
      "Only ii",
      "Only i",
      "Both i and ii",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "correctOption": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "The difference of {1, 2, 3} and {1, 2, 5} is the set ____________",
    "options": [
      "{1}",
      "{5}",
      "{3}",
      "{2}"
    ],
    "correctOption": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "The complement of the set A is _____________",
    "options": [
      "A – B",
      "U – A",
      "A – U",
      "B – A"
    ],
    "correctOption": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "The bit string for the set {2, 4, 6, 8, 10} (with universal set of natural numbers less than or equal to 10) is ____________________",
    "options": [
      "0101010101",
      "1010101010",
      "1010010101",
      "0010010101"
    ],
    "correctOption": 0
  }
]
}